Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Records SC0282
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-272
  - Trustee Reunion, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Trustee Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Trustee Handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Who's Who Background, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Who's Who Background, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Who's Who Background, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Who's Who Background, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Who's Who Background, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Updated Who's Who, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Who's Who Background, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Who's Who Background, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Who's Who Background, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Committee members, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Committee members, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Committee members, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Committee members, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Committee members, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Student Committee members, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Student Committee members, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Student Committee members, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hood & Gowns former trustees (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-236
  - Invitation for dinner in honor of President John L. Hennessy and Mrs. Andrea Hennessy, 2016 Jun 8 (Box 1)